export const Languages = [
  {
    name: "English",
    id: "en",
  },
  {
    name: "Español",
    id: "es",
  },
  {
    name: "हिन्दी",
    id: "hi",
  },
  {
    name: "Português",
    id: "pt",
  },
  {
    name: "中文",
    id: "zh",
  },
  {
    name: "Français",
    id: "fr",
  },
];

export const translations = {
  en: {
    TopQ: "Top Questions",
    AllQ: "All Questions",
    AskQ: "Ask Question",
    Loading: "Loading...",
    questions: "questions",
    votes: "votes",
    answers: "answers",
    asked: "asked",
    home: "Home",
    public: "PUBLIC",
    tags: "Tags",
    users: "Users",
    about: "About",
    products: "Products",
    forTeams: "For Teams",
    search: "Search...",
    login: "Log in",
    logout: "Log out",
    askQuestion: "Ask a public Question",
    specific:
      "Be specific and imagine you’re asking a question to another person",
    title: "Title",
    askQplaceholder:
      "e.g. Is there an R function for finding the index of an element in a vector?",
    askQplaceholder2: "e.g. (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "Body",
    include:
      "Include all the information someone would need to answer your question",
    reviewQ: "Reivew your question",
    add: "Add up to 5 tags to describe what your question is about",
    share: "Share",
    delete: "Delete",
    answered: "answered",
    yourAnswer: "Your Answer",
    postanswer: "Post Your Answer",
    browse: "Browse other Question tagged",
    or: "or",
    askOwnQuestion: "Ask your own question",
    Observability:
      "Observability is key to the future of software (and your DevOps career)",
    Podcast: "Podcast 374: How valuable is your screen name?",
    Review: "Review queue workflows - Final release....",
    Associates:
      "Please welcome Valued Associates: #958 - V2Blast #959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated:
      "Outdated Answers: accepted answer is now unpinned on Stack Overflow",
    Spam: "Why was this spam flag declined, yet the question marked as spam?",
    Action:
      "What is the best course of action when a user has high enough rep to...",
    Link: "Is a link to the How to ask help page a useful comment?",
    joined: "Joined",
    editProfile: "Edit Profile",
    noTags: "0 tags watched",
    noBio: "No bio found",
    edit: "Edit Your Profile",
    publicInfo: "Public information",
    displayName: "Display name",
    aboutMe: "About me",
    addTags: "Add tags separated by a space",
    save: "Save profile",
    cancel: "Cancel",
  },

  es: {
    TopQ: "Top preguntas",
    AllQ: "Todas las preguntas",
    AskQ: "Preguntar una pregunta",
    Loading: "Cargando...",
    questions: "preguntas",
    votes: "votos",
    answers: "respuestas",
    asked: "preguntado",
    home: "Casa",
    public: "PUBLICO",
    tags: "etiquetas",
    users: "usuarios",
    about: "acerca de",
    products: "productos",
    forTeams: "para Equipos",
    search: "Buscar...",
    login: "Iniciar sesión",
    logout: "salir",
    askQuestion: "Preguntar una pregunta publica",
    specific:
      "Sea especifico y imagine que estás preguntando una pregunta a otro usuario",
    title: "Título",
    askQplaceholder:
      "por ejemplo, ¿hay alguna función en R para encontrar el índice de un elemento en un vector?",
    askQplaceholder2: "por ejemplo, (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "Cuerpo",
    include:
      "Incluya toda la información que alguien necesita para responder tu pregunta",
    reviewQ: "Revisar tu pregunta",
    add: "Añade hasta 5 etiquetas para describir que tu pregunta es sobre",
    share: "Comparte",
    delete: "borrar",
    answered: "respondido",
    yourAnswer: "Tu respuesta",
    postanswer: "Publicar tu respuesta",
    browse: "Navegar preguntas etiquetadas",
    or: "o",
    askOwnQuestion: "Preguntar a tu propia pregunta",
    Observability:
      "Observabilidad es clave para el futuro de software (y tu carrera en DevOps)",
    Podcast: "Podcast 374: ¿Cál es valioso tu nombre de pantalla?",
    Review: "Revision de flujos de trabajo - Lanzamiento final...",
    Associates:
      "¡Bienvenido a los Asociados Valorados: #958 - V2Blast #959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated:
      "Respuestas obsoletas: respuesta aceptada ya no se pone en el pin de la respuesta",
    Spam: "¿Por qué fue este spam rechazado, y la pregunta marcada como spam?",
    Action:
      "¿Cual es el mejor curso de accion cuando un usuario tiene suficiente rep para...",
    Link: "¿Es un enlace a la página de ayuda de Stack Overflow una buena comentario?",
    joined: "Ingresó",
    editProfile: "Editar perfil",
    noTags: "0 etiquetas seguidas",
    noBio: "No se encontró biografía",
    edit: "Editar tu perfil",
    publicInfo: "Información pública",
    displayName: "Nombre visible",
    aboutMe: "Acerca de mí",
    addTags: "Agregar etiquetas separadas por espacio",
    save: "Guardar perfil",
    cancel: "Cancelar",
  },

  hi: {
    TopQ: "शीर्ष प्रश्न",
    AllQ: "सभी प्रश्न",
    AskQ: "प्रश्न पूछें",
    Loading: "लोड हो रहा है...",
    questions: "प्रश्न",
    votes: "वोट",
    answers: "उत्तर",
    asked: "पूछा गया",
    home: "होम",
    public: "सार्वजनिक",
    tags: "टैग",
    users: "उपयोगकर्ता",
    about: "के बारे में",
    products: "उत्पाद",
    forTeams: "टीम्स के लिए",
    search: "खोजें...",
    login: "लॉग इन करें",
    logout: "लॉग आउट",
    askQuestion: "सार्वजनिक प्रश्न पूछें",
    specific:
      "स्पष्ट और कल्पना करें कि आप किसी दूसरे व्यक्ति से प्रश्न पूछ रहे हैं",
    title: "शीर्षक",
    askQplaceholder:
      "उदाहरण के लिए, क्या वेक्टर में एक तत्व के सूचकांक ढूंढने के लिए एक आर फ़ंक्शन है?",
    askQplaceholder2: "उदाहरण के लिए, (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "शरीर",
    include: "अपने प्रश्न का उत्तर देने के लिए सभी जानकारी शामिल करें",
    reviewQ: "प्रश्न समीक्षा करें",
    add: "अपने प्रश्न के विषय को वर्णित करने के लिए तकनीकी टैग जोड़ें",
    share: "साझा करें",
    delete: "हटाएं",
    answered: "उत्तर दिया गया",
    yourAnswer: "आपका उत्तर",
    postanswer: "उत्तर पोस्ट करें",
    browse: "अन्य टैग किए गए प्रश्न ब्राउज़ करें",
    or: "या",
    askOwnQuestion: "अपना सवाल पूछें",
    Observability:
      "ऑब्सर्वेबिलिटी सॉफ़्टवेयर के भविष्य (और आपके डेवऑप्स करियर) के लिए महत्वपूर्ण है",
    Podcast: "पॉडकास्ट 374: आपके स्क्रीन नाम कितना मूल्यवान है?",
    Review: "समीक्षा कतार वर्कफ़्लो - अंतिम रिलीज....",
    Associates:
      "कृपया स्वागत करें Valued Associates: #958 - V2Blast #959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated: "आउटडेट उत्तर: स्वीकृत उत्तर अब स्टैक ओवरफ़्लो पर अनपिन है",
    Spam: "इस जालसाजी झंडा को क्यों अस्वीकृत किया गया, फिर भी प्रश्न को जालसाजी के रूप में चिह्नित किया गया?",
    Action:
      "जब एक उपयोगकर्ता के पास पर्याप्त प्रतिष्ठा होती है, तो सबसे अच्छा कार्य क्या है?",
    Link: "क्या 'कैसे पूछने' मदद पृष्ठ का एक लिंक एक उपयोगी टिप्पणी है?",
    joined: "शामिल हुए",
    editProfile: "प्रोफ़ाइल संपादित करें",
    noTags: "0 टैग देखे गए",
    noBio: "कोई जीवनी नहीं मिली",
    edit: "अपना प्रोफ़ाइल संपादित करें",
    publicInfo: "सार्वजनिक जानकारी",
    displayName: "प्रदर्शन नाम",
    aboutMe: "मेरे बारे में",
    addTags: "अंतरित स्थान द्वारा टैग जोड़ें",
    save: "प्रोफ़ाइल सहेजें",
    cancel: "रद्द करें",
  },

  pt: {
    TopQ: "Principais Questões",
    AllQ: "Todas as Questões",
    AskQ: "Fazer uma Pergunta",
    Loading: "Carregando...",
    questions: "questões",
    votes: "votos",
    answers: "respostas",
    asked: "perguntado",
    home: "Início",
    public: "PÚBLICO",
    tags: "Tags",
    users: "Usuários",
    about: "Sobre",
    products: "Produtos",
    forTeams: "Para Equipes",
    search: "Pesquisar",
    login: "Entrar",
    logout: "Sair",
    askQuestion: "Fazer uma Pergunta Pública",
    specific:
      "Seja específico e imagine que você está fazendo uma pergunta para outra pessoa",
    title: "Título",
    askQplaceholder:
      "por exemplo, existe alguma função em R para encontrar o índice de um elemento em um vetor?",
    askQplaceholder2: "por exemplo (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "Corpo",
    include:
      "Inclua todas as informações que alguém precisa para responder sua pergunta",
    reviewQ: "Revisar uma Pergunta",
    add: "Adicione até 5 tags para descrever sobre o que sua pergunta é",
    share: "Compartilhar",
    delete: "Excluir",
    answered: "respondida",
    yourAnswer: "Sua Resposta",
    postanswer: "Postar Resposta",
    browse: "Navegue por outras Questões marcadas",
    or: "ou",
    askOwnQuestion: "Faça sua própria pergunta",
    Observability:
      "A observabilidade é fundamental para o futuro do software (e sua carreira em DevOps)",
    Podcast: "Podcast 374: Quão valioso é o seu nome de tela?",
    Review: "Fluxos de trabalho da fila de revisão - Versão final....",
    Associates:
      "Por favor, dê as boas-vindas aos Associados Valiosos: #958 - V2Blast #959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated:
      "Respostas desatualizadas: a resposta aceita agora não está fixada no Stack Overflow",
    Spam: "Por que esta bandeira de spam foi recusada, mas a pergunta foi marcada como spam?",
    Action:
      "Qual é o melhor curso de ação quando um usuário tem reputação alta o suficiente para...",
    Link: "Um link para a página de ajuda 'Como perguntar' é um comentário útil?",
    joined: "Entrou",
    editProfile: "Editar perfil",
    noTags: "0 tags seguidas",
    noBio: "Nenhuma biografia encontrada",
    edit: "Editar seu perfil",
    publicInfo: "Informação pública",
    displayName: "Nome de exibição",
    aboutMe: "Sobre mim",
    addTags: "Adicionar tags separadas por espaço",
    save: "Salvar perfil",
    cancel: "Cancelar",
  },

  zh: {
    TopQ: "热门问题",
    AllQ: "所有问题",
    AskQ: "提问",
    Loading: "加载中...",
    questions: "问题",
    votes: "投票",
    answers: "答案",
    asked: "提问时间",
    home: "首页",
    public: "公开",
    tags: "标签",
    users: "用户",
    about: "关于",
    products: "产品",
    forTeams: "团队",
    search: "搜索",
    login: "登录",
    logout: "登出",
    askQuestion: "提出一个公共问题",
    specific: "具体说明，并设想您向另一个人提问",
    title: "标题",
    askQplaceholder: "例如，在R中是否有一个函数可以找到向量中元素的索引？",
    askQplaceholder2: "例如 (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "正文",
    include: "包含所有回答问题所需的信息",
    reviewQ: "回复一个问题",
    add: "添加最多5个标签以描述您的问题内容",
    share: "分享",
    delete: "删除",
    answered: "已回答",
    yourAnswer: "你的答案",
    postanswer: "提交答案",
    browse: "浏览其他标记的问题",
    or: "或",
    askOwnQuestion: "提出你自己的问题",
    Observability: "可观察性是软件未来发展的关键（以及您的DevOps职业）",
    Podcast: "第374期播客：您的屏幕名称有多有价值？",
    Review: "审查队列工作流程 - 最终发布....",
    Associates: "欢迎Valued Associates：＃958 - V2Blast＃959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated: "过时答案：接受的答案现在在Stack Overflow上取消了固定",
    Spam: "为什么这个垃圾邮件标志被拒绝，而问题却被标记为垃圾邮件？",
    Action: "当用户拥有足够高的声誉时，最佳操作是什么？",
    Link: "链接到“如何提问”帮助页面是否是一个有用的评论？",
    joined: "加入",
    editProfile: "编辑个人资料",
    noTags: "0 个标签关注",
    noBio: "未找到个人简介",
    edit: "编辑您的个人资料",
    publicInfo: "公共信息",
    displayName: "显示名称",
    aboutMe: "关于我",
    addTags: "添加以空格分隔的标签",
    save: "保存个人资料",
    cancel: "取消",
  },

  fr: {
    TopQ: "Meilleures Questions",
    AllQ: "Toutes les Questions",
    AskQ: "Poser une Question",
    Loading: "Chargement...",
    questions: "questions",
    votes: "votes",
    answers: "réponses",
    asked: "posée",
    home: "Accueil",
    public: "PUBLIC",
    tags: "Tags",
    users: "Utilisateurs",
    about: "À propos de",
    products: "Produits",
    forTeams: "Pour les Équipes",
    search: "Rechercher",
    login: "Se connecter",
    logout: "Se déconnecter",
    askQuestion: "Poser une Question Publique",
    specific:
      "Soyez précis et imaginez que vous posez une question à une autre personne",
    title: "Titre",
    askQplaceholder:
      "par exemple, existe-t-il une fonction en R pour trouver l'index d'un élément dans un vecteur ?",
    askQplaceholder2: "par exemple (xml typescript wordpress)",
    body: "Corps",
    include:
      "Incluez toutes les informations nécessaires pour répondre à votre question",
    reviewQ: "Reviser une Question",
    add: "Ajoutez jusqu'à 5 tags pour décrire le sujet de votre question",
    share: "Partager",
    delete: "Supprimer",
    answered: "répondue",
    yourAnswer: "Votre Réponse",
    postanswer: "Poser une Reponse",
    browse: "Parcourir d'autres Questions étiquetées",
    or: "ou",
    askOwnQuestion: "Posez votre Propre Question",
    Observability:
      "L'observabilité est essentielle pour l'avenir du logiciel (et votre carrière DevOps)",
    Podcast: "Podcast 374 : Quelle valeur a votre pseudonyme ?",
    Review:
      "Flux de travail de la file d'attente de révision - Version finale....",
    Associates:
      "Veuillez accueillir les Associés Précieux : #958 - V2Blast #959 - SpencerG",
    Outdated:
      "Réponses obsolètes : la réponse acceptée n'est plus épinglée sur Stack Overflow",
    Spam: "Pourquoi ce signalement de spam a été refusé, alors que la question était marquée comme spam ?",
    Action:
      "Quelle est la meilleure action à entreprendre quand un utilisateur a une réputation suffisamment élevée pour...",
    Link: "Un lien vers la page d'aide 'Comment poser une question' est-il un commentaire utile ?",
    joined: "Rejoint",
    editProfile: "Modifier le profil",
    noTags: "0 tags suivis",
    noBio: "Aucune biographie trouvée",
    edit: "Modifier votre profil",
    publicInfo: "Informations publiques",
    displayName: "Nom d'affichage",
    aboutMe: "À propos de moi",
    addTags: "Ajouter des tags séparés par un espace",
    save: "Enregistrer le profil",
    cancel: "Annuler",
  },
};
